request recently changes update or claim
policy Sun Life here's how to check via
service request first log to your
sunlife pH mobile app go to service
request tab sa bang bottom navigation
bar then choose track my request service
requestm
display for request with awaiting
requirement
status or click comments from sunlife
Team related request to submit
additional documents Nam click on top to
upload then check the take box to
confirm authenticity of the documents
top update request for more inquiries
you may contact our client care at 88
84988 188 whether email sunlink
sunlife.com
or Cent Port link
and mobile app for more information tune
in to this page thank you